# Faisal Aljaghthami

# Software Engineer, UX/UI Designer, Front-End Web Developer

# +966549024660 | fayeharbi@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/faisalaljaghathami

# **Summary**

A Software Engineer with a Nanodegree in UX Design, experienced in UX/UI Design, Web Development, Quality Assurance, Public Relations, and Project Management.

Interested in researching new ideas and techniques to create impactful experiences for users through UX/UI. Ambitious, cheerful, observant, and love to learn new skills and go through new experiences.

#### **Skills**

o UX/UI Design

Public Relations

o Communication skills

- Web Development
- Project Management
- o Problem Solving

- Quality Assurance
- o Data Analysis

Time management

#### **Education**

## Bachelors' degree in Software Engineering – University of Jeddah

- o Honors Class, GPA: 4.5/5
- Vice President of the "Future Leaders Committee".
- Volunteer at "Makkah days for programming and AI" held by the Emirate of Makkah.

Nanodegree in User Experience Design – Udacity

### **Work Experiences**

IT Specialist – Saudia Airlines	Aug 2022 - Oct 2022
Front-End Web Developer – Avant Gaea	Apr 2022 - Jul 2022
Quality Assurance Engineer – Brainnest	Jan 2022 - Mar 2022
UX/UI Designer – Etiq AI	Sep 2021 - Dec 2021
Public Relations Specialist – Google Developer Student Clubs	Jul 2020 - Aug 2021

# **Professional Certificates**

- SFC Scrum Fundamentals Certified SCRUMstudy Accreditation Body for Scrum and Agile
- GRCP Governance, Risk Management, Compliance Professional OCEG
- o **UX Design Professional Certificate** Google
- o **Project Management Professional Certificate** Google
- o Data Analytics Professional Certificate Google
- o CTFL Certified Tester Foundation Level Certification Training Udemy
- o ITIL v4 Foundation Certification Training Udemy
- o **Devops Foundation Certification Training** Udemy